Artificial and Ephemera 060
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Sports - Stadiums - National Memorial Stadium, 1956-11-08 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Sports - Stadiums - Stadium Reference Material, 1945-03 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Stickers - Stickers - Stickers (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Streets - H Street, NW - H Street, NW, 1830-10-14 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Streets - Georgia Avenue - Georgia Avenue, 1994-10-17 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Streets - Park Place, NW - Park Place, NW, 1907-1910 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Streets - Park Road - Park Road, 1910-1947 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Streets - Pennsylvania Avenue - Pennsylvania Avenue, 1841-1971 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Streets - Pennsylvania Avenue - Pennsylvania Avenue, Route of Residents, 1957-01 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Streets - Pennsylvania Avenue - Walking Guides (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Streets - Princeton Place, NW - Princeton Place, NW, 1910 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Streets - Pomander Walk - Pomander Walk, 1963-01 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Streets - Prospect Street - Prospect Street, 1936 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Synagogues - Ohev Sholom Talmud Torah - Ohev Sholom Talmud Torah, 2006-02 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Synagogues - Washington Hebrew Congregation - Washington Hebrew Congregation, 1950-02-08 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- Theatre and Theatres - Theatres - Theatres (Box 51, Folder 16)
- Theatre and Theatres - Actors' Center - Actors' Center, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Theatre and Theatres - Arnindia - Arnindia, 1938 (Box 51, Folder 18)
- Theatre and Theatres - Art Students' League - Art Students' League, 1895-03-27 (Box 51, Folder 19)
- Theatre and Theatres - B. F. Keith's - B. F. Keith's, 1924-09-21 (Box 51, Folder 20)
- Theatre and Theatres - Belasco Theatre - Belasco Theatre, 1936 (Box 51, Folder 21)
- Theatre and Theatres - Central High School - Central High School, 1922-12-23 (Box 51, Folder 22)
- Theatre and Theatres - Chevy Chase Franties, The - Chevy Chase Franties, The, 1936-03-04 (Box 51, Folder 23)
- Theatre and Theatres - Chevy Chase School Theatre - Chevy Chase School Theatre, ca. 1930 (Box 51, Folder 24)
- Theatre and Theatres - Columbia Theatre - Columbia Theatre, 1915-06-11 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  RMS Titanic?
- Theatre and Theatres - Community Theater - Community Theater, 1960-02 (Box 51, Folder 26)
- Theatre and Theatres - Ford's Opera House - Ford's Opera House, 1878-04-23 (Box 51, Folder 27)
- Theatre and Theatres - Gunston Hall - Gunston Hall, 1906-1936 (Box 51, Folder 28)
- Theatre and Theatres - Helen Hayes Awards - Helen Hayes Awards, 1989-2002 (Box 51, Folder 29)
- Theatre and Theatres - Howard Theatre - Howard Theatre, 1940-06-02 (Box 51, Folder 30)
- Theatre and Theatres - Kennedy Center - Kennedy Center, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 31)
- Theatre and Theatres - Knickerbocker Theatre - Knickerbocker Theatre, 1922-01-28 (Box 51, Folder 32)
- Theatre and Theatres - Knickerbocker Theatre - "The Storm", 1922 (Box 51, Folder 33)
- Theatre and Theatres - National Theatre - National Theatre, 1892-1940 (Box 51, Folder 34)
- Theatre and Theatres - New Academy - New Academy (Box 51, Folder 35)
- Theatre and Theatres - Onstage - Onstage, 1986-05 (Box 51, Folder 36)
- Theatre and Theatres - Ontario Theatre - Ontario Theatre, ca. 1950 (Box 51, Folder 37)
- Theatre and Theatres - Players - Players (Box 51, Folder 38)
- Theatre and Theatres - Prince of Peace Players, The - Prince of Peace Players, The, ca. 1940 (Box 51, Folder 39)
- Theatre and Theatres - Productions Incorporated - Productions Incorporated, ca. 1949 (Box 51, Folder 40)
- Theatre and Theatres - Studio, the - Studio, the, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 41)
- Theatre and Theatres - Studio Marionettes - Studio Marionettes, 1938-02-10 (Box 51, Folder 42)
- Theatre and Theatres - Temple Players, The - Temple Players, The (Box 51, Folder 43)
- Theatre and Theatres - Theatre Lobby - Theatre Lobby, 1954-03 (Box 51, Folder 44)
- Theatre and Theatres - Theatrecraft - Theatrecraft (Box 51, Folder 45)
- Theatre and Theatres - Uptown Theatre - Uptown Theatre, 1936-10-29 (Box 51, Folder 46)
- Theatre and Theatres - Uptown Theatre - Scott Joplin, 1977-02-18 (Box 51, Folder 47)
- Theatre and Theatres - Washington Stage Guild - Washington Stage Guild, 2006-04-20 (Box 51, Folder 48)
- Theatre and Theatres - Washington Theatre - Washington Theratre (Box 51, Folder 49)
- Theatre and Theatres - Washington Theatre Alliance, The - Washington Theatre Alliance, The, 1947-05 (Box 51, Folder 50)
- Theatre and Theatres - Washington Wellsley Club, The - Washington Wellsley Club, The (Box 51, Folder 51)
- Theatre and Theatres - Western High School Auditorium - Western High School Auditorium, 1906-1930 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Theatre and Theatres - Willard Hotel - Willard Hotel (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Theatre and Theatres - Woodley Players, The - Woodley Players, The, 1955-01 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Tickets - Tickets - Tickets, ca. 1950 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Tickets - American Ice Company - American Ice Company (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Tickets - Arena Stage - Arena Stage, 1973-11-20 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Tickets - Armstrong High School - Armstrong High School, 1937-04-06 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Tickets - Basketball - Basketball, 1982-02-12 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Tickets - Constitution Hall - Constitution Hall, 1963-1971 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Tickets - Dance - Dance, 1930-1934 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Tickets - Drill Comprtitions - Drill Comprtitions, 1928-06-05 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Tickets - Fireman's Relief Fund - Fireman's Relief Fund, 1929-09-02-1940-09-14 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Tickets - First Baptist Church - First Baptist Church (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Tickets - Flag Day - Flag Day, 1916-06-14 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Tickets - Football - Football, 1928-12-01 (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Tickets - George Washington University - George Washington University, 1929 (Box 52, Folder 16)
- Tickets - Golf - Golf (Box 52, Folder 17)
- Tickets - House of Repersentatives - House of Repersentatives, 1892-05-06 (Box 52, Folder 18)
- Tickets - Kennedy Center - Kennedy Center, 1971-09-08 (Box 52, Folder 19)
- Tickets - Lectures - Lectures (Box 52, Folder 20)
- Tickets - Lisner Auditorium - Lisner Auditorium, 1964-03-18 (Box 52, Folder 21)
- Tickets - Machinists' Lunch - Machinists' Lunch (Box 52, Folder 22)
- Tickets - Metropolitan Theatre - Metropolitan Theatre, 1965-04-30 (Box 52, Folder 23)
- Tickets - Monarch Radio Shop - Monarch Radio Shop, 1930 (Box 52, Folder 24)
- Tickets - National Theatre - National Theatre, 1933-1939 (Box 52, Folder 25)
- Tickets - Parking Lots - Parking Lots (Box 52, Folder 26)
- Tickets - Pick the Oscars - Pick the Oscars, 1965-04-15 (Box 52, Folder 27)
- Tickets - Playhouse, The - Playhouse, The (Box 52, Folder 28)
- Tickets - Track Meets - Track Meets, 1931-05-16 (Box 52, Folder 29)
- Tickets - Treasury Department - Treasury Department, 1916-06-14 (Box 52, Folder 30)
- Tickets - United Food Stores Exposition - United Food Stores Exposition (Box 52, Folder 31)
- Tickets - United States Senate Chamber - United States Senate Chamber, 1922-04-25 (Box 52, Folder 32)
- Tickets - Washington Auditorium - Washington Auditorium, 1928-1933 (Box 52, Folder 33)
- Tickets - Washington Bicentennial - Washington Bicentennial, ca. 1932 (Box 52, Folder 34)
- Tickets - Willard Hotel - Willard Hotel, 1928-11-30 (Box 52, Folder 35)
- Tourism - Tourism - Tourism, 1906-1951 (Box 52, Folder 36)
- Tourism - Children's Tours and Lectures Projects - Children's Tours and Lectures Projects, 1947-01-24 (Box 52, Folder 37)
- Tourism - Guide Books - Close up of Washington, 1958 (Box 52, Folder 38)
- Tourism - Guide Books - Greeters' Guide to Washington, 1923 (Box 52, Folder 39)
- Tourism - Guide Books - Greeters' Guide to Washington, 1926 (Box 52, Folder 40)
- Tourism - Guide Books - Greeters' Guide to Washington, 1937 (Box 52, Folder 41)
- Tourism - Guide Books - Greeters' Guide to Washington, 1927 (Box 52, Folder 42)
- Tourism - Guide Books - "Guide to Washington" by Marie Fromuth, 1961 (Box 52, Folder 43)
- Tourism - Guide Books - Guide to Washington and Its Vicinity, 1878 (Box 52, Folder 44)
- Tourism - Guide Books - This Week in the Nation's Capital, 1941-08-31 (Box 52, Folder 45)
- Tourism - Guide Books - Tourist's Guide to Washington and Its Vicinity, 1880 (Box 52, Folder 46)
- Tourism - Guide Books - Triangle Tours Bicentennial Special, The, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 47)
- Tourism - Guide Books - Visitors Guide, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 48)
- Tourism - Guide Books - Washington and Its Environs (Box 52, Folder 49)
- Tourism - Guide Books - Washington DC, The Nation's Beautiful White City, 1924 (Box 52, Folder 50)
- Tourism - Guide Books - Wasington Handy Guide, 1941 (Box 52, Folder 51)
- Tourism - Guide Books - Washington Practical Guide, 1939 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Tourism - Guide Books - Washington the National Capital (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Tourism - Guide Books - Washington the Place of Pilgrimage for Petriotic Amecicans, 1925 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Tourism - Guide Books - Weekend Tour Washington DC (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Tourism - Highlights of the National Capital and its Historic Environs - Highlights of the National Capital and its Historic Environs (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Tourism - Pamphlets - Ameican Sightseeing Tours (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Tourism - Pamphlets - Capital Traction Company (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Tourism - Pamphlets - D.C. Transit System, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Tourism - Pamphlets - Grayline, The, 1944-1970 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Tourism - Pamphlets - International Auto Sightseeing Transit Company, ca. 1944 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Tourism - Pamphlets - Milling Tours (Box 53, Folder 11)
- Tourism - Pamphlets - Shoreham Hotel, 1938 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Tourism - Pamphlets - Sight-Seeing Automobile Coach (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Tourism - Pamphlets - Tourmobile, ca. 1974 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- Tourism - Pamphlets - Washington Board of Trade (Box 53, Folder 15)
- Tourism - Pamphlets - Washington Cathedral (Box 53, Folder 16)
- Tourism - Pamphlets - Washington Convention and Visitors Bureau, 1962-1970 (Box 53, Folder 17)
- Tourism - Pamphlets - Washington Sightseeing Tours, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 18)
- Tourism - Pamphlets - Woodward and Lothrop, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 19)
- Tourism - Points of Interest - Points of Interest, ca. 1943 (Box 53, Folder 20)
- Tourism - Points of Special Interest - Points of Special Interest, ca. 1940 (Box 53, Folder 21)
- Tourism - Recovery of Tourism in the District of Columbia - Recovery of Tourism in the District of Columbia, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 22)
- Tourism - Seeing the Nation's Capital - Seeing the Nation's Capital, ca. 1950 (Box 53, Folder 23)
- Tourism - Seeing Washington - Seeing Washington, ca. 1940 (Box 53, Folder 24)
- Tourism - Sight-Seeing Guides - Sight-Seeing Guides, ca. 1950 (Box 53, Folder 25)
- Tourism - Sightseeing Guide - Sightseeing Guide, ca. 1945 (Box 53, Folder 26)
- Tourism - So ... You Want to See Washington - So ... You Want to See Washington (Box 53, Folder 27)
- Tourism - Tour of the Week: Historical Washington - Tour of the Week: Historical Washington (Box 53, Folder 28)
- Tourism - Tourism Travel and the Bicentennial - Tourism Travel and the Bicentennial, 1972-11 (Box 53, Folder 29)
- Tourism - Washington DC Convention Facilities - Washington DC Convention Facilities (Box 53, Folder 30)
- Transportation - Transportation - Transportation, 1942-1982 (Box 53, Folder 31)
- Transportation - An Approach to the Mass Transportation Problem for the District of Columbia - An Approach to the Mass Transportation Problem for the District of Columbia, 1952-12 (Box 53, Folder 32)
- Transportation - Boats - "New Ferrt-Boat 'Woodburt'" by Edwin Fulton Rorebeck, 1905-10 (Box 53, Folder 33)
- Transportation - Boats - Norfolk and Washington Steamboat Company (Box 53, Folder 34)
- Transportation - Buses - Metrobus (Box 53, Folder 35)
- Transportation - Buses - Museum Bus (Box 53, Folder 36)
- Transportation - Busses and Rail - Capital Transit Company, 1936-1956 (Box 53, Folder 37)
- Transportation - Busses and Rail - DC Transit, 1956-1970 (Box 54, Folder 38)
- Transportation - Highways and Roads - Highways and Roads, 1968-1969 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Transportation - Highways and Roads - Highway User, The, 1963-02 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Transportation - Legislation - Legislation, 1955-1965 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Transportation - Railway - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, ca. 1940 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Transportation - Railway - Capital Traction Company, 1926-02-15 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Transportation - Railway - DC Rapid Rail, 1964-11 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Transportation - Railway - Metro, 2002-2004 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Transportation - Railway - Metropolitan Railroad Company, 1864 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Transportation - Railway - Washington and Eckington Railroad, 1894 (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Transportation - Railway - Washington, Frederick and Gettysburg Railway Company (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Transportation - Railway - Washington-Virginia Railway (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Transportation - Schedules and Fares - Schedules and Fares, 1962-05-31 (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Transportation - Stagecoach - Phoenix Line, 1835-11-13 (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Transportation - Technical Notes - Technical Notes, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 14)
- Transportation - Transportation Needs of Special Urban Groups - Transportation Needs of Special Urban Groups, 1969-04 (Box 54, Folder 15)
- Transportation - Transportation Planning Board Annual Report - Transportation Planning Board Annual Report, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Transportation - Washington Handy Book: A Street Directory Trolley Guide and Map - Washington Handy Book: A Street Directory Trolley Guide and Map (Box 54, Folder 17)
- Transportation - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (WMATA) - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (WMATA), 1954-1968 (Box 54, Folder 18)
- Transportation - Washington Transportation Study - Washington Transportation Study, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 19)
- Trees - Famous and Historic Trees of the City of Washington - "Famous and Historic Trees of the City of Washington" by Edna Jane Roberts, 1927 (Box 54, Folder 20)
- Trees - Famous Trees of Washington - "Famous Trees of Washington" by Charles F. Nesbit, 1946-01 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  Mauuscript
- Trees - "Fosest Trees of the District of Columbia" by Wilbur R. Mattoon - "Fosest Trees of the District of Columbia" by Wilbur R. Mattoon, 1926 (Box 54, Folder 22)
- Trees - Neglect of the Trees - Neglect of the Trees, 1905-07-09 (Box 54, Folder 23)
- Trees - Report for the Press - Report for the Press, 1959-05-22 (Box 54, Folder 24)
- Trees - Tree System of Washington, The - Tree System of Washington, The, 1917-02-08 (Box 54, Folder 25)
- Trees - Trees in Washington - Trees in Washington, 1921-04-12 (Box 54, Folder 26)
- Water Supply - Water Supply - Water Supply, 1852-1939 (Box 54, Folder 27)
- Water Supply - Water Supply - Water Supply, 1938-1947 (Box 54, Folder 28)
- Water Supply - District of Columbia - "District of Columbia" by V. C. Fishel, 1942 (Box 54, Folder 29)
- Water Supply - Effect of the 1930 Drought on the Washington Water Supply, The - "Effect of the 1930 Drought on the Washington Water Supply, The" by Carl J. Lauter, 1932-01-01 (Box 54, Folder 30)
- Water Supply - Metropolitan Water Problems - Metropolitan Water Problems, 1958-03 (Box 54, Folder 31)
- Water Supply - Water Rent - Water Rent, 1911-1920 (Box 54, Folder 32)
- Waterfront - Waterfront - Waterfront, 1956-1978 (Box 54, Folder 33)
- World War I - World War I - World War I, 1918-1922 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- World War I - Community Service Training School for Leaders of Recreation - Community Service Training School for Leaders of Recreation, 1919 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- World War I - Dedication of Memorial Trees to Men and Women of the District of Columbia - Dedication of Memorial Trees to Men and Women of the District of Columbia, 1920-05-30 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- World War I - Victory Parade - Victory Parade, 1919-07-04 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- World War I - War-Time Washington - War-Time Washington, 1918-03 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- World War I - War Workers' Handbook - War Workers' Handbook, 1918 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- World War II - World War II - World War II, 1941-1942 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- World War II - Arfican Americans - African Americans, ca. 1945 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- World War II - Draft Aid Center - Draft Aid Center, 1944-04 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- World War II - Salvage - Salvage, 1943-1945 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- World War II - Salvage - Battle Flags for Action on the Home Front, ca. 1942 (Box 55, Folder 11)
- World War II - Salvage - DC Salvage Committee, 1942-1944 (Box 55, Folder 12)
- World War II - Salvage - Double Duty, 1942 (Box 55, Folder 13)
- World War II - Salvage - Flags Abreast, 1944-1945 (Box 55, Folder 14)
- World War II - Salvage - Salvage for Victory, 1942 (Box 55, Folder 15)
- World War II - Salvage - Victory Book Campaign, 1942 (Box 55, Folder 16)
- World War II - Veterans Information - Veterans Information, ca. 1945 (Box 55, Folder 17)
- World War II - Victory Gardens - Victory Gardens, 1945 (Box 55, Folder 18)
- World War II - Wartime Washington - Wartime Washington, 1942-02-27 (Box 55, Folder 19)
- World War II - Women - Women, 1943-1999 (Box 55, Folder 20)
- World War II - Women - Good Leave Town, A, 1947 (Box 55, Folder 21)
- World War II - Women - Havelock, The, 1944-1945 (Box 55, Folder 22)
- Zoo - Geologic Exhibits in the National Zoological Park - "Geologic Exhibits in the National Zoological Park" by R. S. Bassler, 1940 (Box 55, Folder 23)
- Zoo - Who's Who at the Zoo - Who's Who at the Zoo, 1946 (Box 55, Folder 24)